<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE section PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY yast "YaST">
<!ENTITY suse "SUSE">
<!ENTITY suselinux "&suse; Linux">
<!ENTITY opensuse "openSUSE">
<!ENTITY suse-version "11.1">
]>
<!-- <table cellspacing="10" cellpadding="5"> -->
<!--   <tr> -->
<!--     <td valign="top"><img src="&imagedir;/01_welcome.png" width="150" valign="top"></td> -->
<!--     <td> -->

<section>
 <title>Slide Show</title>

<section label="01_welcome">
  <title>Welcome to SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop</title>

<para>SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop is the industry's leading
enterprise-quality Linux operating system that's optimized and ready
for both business and personal use. SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop
provides market-leading usability, seamless interoperability with
existing enterprise computer systems, and dozens of essential office
applications that enable businesses to use Linux and open source with
confidence. Designed for general-purpose use, SUSE Linux Enterprise
Desktop can also be tailored to fit fixed-function or special-purpose
roles such as on technical workstations, kiosks, and thin clients.</para>
</section>
<section label="02_innovation">
  <title>The Latest Desktop Innovations</title>

<para>Novell's leadership in desktop innovation is unparalleled. Combining
results from extensive and ongoing usability studies with an outstanding
technology vision, Novell introduces SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop 11 as
the most integrated and powerful Linux desktop. SUSE Linux Enterprise
Desktop can be installed on a wide range of client devices including
desktops, notebooks, netbooks, nettops, workstations, and more and
includes all of the applications you need to be productive at work
or home.</para>

<para>Novell's sponsorship and industry leadership in key open source
projects such as the Linux kernel, OpenOffice.org, GNOME, Evolution,
NetworkManager, Banshee, Mono, Compiz, F-Spot, Beagle, and many others
illustrate Novell's unmatched innovation in the Linux desktop.</para>

</section>
<section label="03_connect">
  <title>Connect and Communicate</title>

  <para>SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop 11 provides all the tools you need
  to communicate with the world.</para>

  <para>The Firefox Web browser is the best Web browser in the market. It
  boasts a complete set of browser features and lightning-fast performance
  out of the box, and delivers a rich user experience through plug-ins
  such as Java, Novell Moonlight, Adobe Acrobat Reader, and Adobe
  Flash Player, which are all included in SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop
  11.</para>

  <para>Novell Evolution is a complete collaboration client suite
  supporting collaboration open standards. It includes Novell GroupWise
  and Microsoft Exchange connectivity for messaging, contact management,
  calendaring and task management.</para>

 <para>SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop also includes an instant messaging
 client that lets you connect with people all over the world.</para>

 <para>So to always have you online NetworkManager, our easy-to-use
 network configuration tool can access the most complex and secured
 networks, including WEP, WPA, VPN and other technologies, or simply
 the open wireless network from your coffee shop. Making sure to keep
 connected to the Internet, no matter where you are.</para>

</section>
<section label="04_office">
  <title>Spreadsheets, Presentations, Text Documents and More</title>
  <para>SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop comes complete with the latest
  version of the leading open source office productivity suite,
  OpenOffice.org. OpenOffice.org Novell Edition comes with word
  processing, spreadsheet, presentation, database, and drawing
  applications.</para>

<para>As the leading alternative to Microsoft Office, OpenOffice.org
Novell Edition fully supports the latest open document format standards,
the widest range of Microsoft Office file formats and many others.</para>

<para>OpenOffice.org Novell Edition also provides enhanced VBA macro
support, an improved Solver, and pivot table capability. To spice up all
your presentations, OpenOffice.org Novell Edition has great new slide
transitions that nicely blend with our desktop effects.</para>

</section>
<section label="05_music">
  <title>Banshee: Manage your Media library</title>

<para>Novell is proud to sponsor the open source Banshee project,
the easy-to-use and beautifully polished media management application.
Listen to music, manage you music library, burn your own music CDs, or
synchronize your music to your portable media player or smartphone so
you listen to your music on the go. Banshee also gives you the ability
to subscribe to a variety of sources, including streamed music and
podcasts.</para>

<para>To ensure the highest quality recordings and playback, Novell
developed its own state of the art Advanced Audio Coding (AAC) encoder
and decoder.</para>

<para>New to SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop 11, Banshee enables you to
include videos into your media library, effortlessly letting you get
entertained and up to date with video podcasts directly from your Linux
desktop. Synchronize video podcasts to your  portable media player for
viewing on the go.</para>

<para>Discover new music through the use of greatly integrated web
services like Last.fm radio.</para>

</section>
<section label="06_graphics">
  <title>Photos, Images, Drawings, Graphics</title>

<para>Our Photo management tool in SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop could
very well be the most user-friendly one ever invented. Recognizing
virtually all digital cameras and photo storage devices automatically,
F-Spot will let you in very few clicks import and manage all your
photos. It keeps an original copy of your photos, allowing you to be
creative and try all kind of modifications while making sure you never
lose any of those precious snapshots again. And uploading pictures to the
Internet has never been easier. Whether it is for printing or for your
friends and family to enjoy, your photos are just 1-click away.</para>


<para>For advanced image manipulation and graphics creation, the
open-source community created GIMP. It is a fantastic and a complete
photo retouching, image composition, and image authoring application. GIMP
has enough features to satisfy the most exacting artist.</para>

<para>Wondering about advanced vector graphics? Then Inkscape is for
you. It is a versatile graphics solution using the W3C standard Scalable
Vector Graphics (SVG) file format. Inkscape natively supports opening
or importing SVG, SVGZ (gzipped SVG), PDF, and AI (Adobe Illustrator)
formats.</para>

</section>
<section label="07_greenIT">
  <title>Linux helps reduce your carbon footprint</title>

<para>We are concerned about the environment. Whether you are a mobile
worker or desktop user, SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop reduces your
power consumption without impacting your productivity in any way. With
increasing reliability, the system will maximize energy saving and will
even let you track it.</para>

<para>Now with effective power management at the processor, chipsets,
platform and operating system level, Novell and its partners optimize
power consumption in order to provide you with the longest possible
battery life.</para>

<para>Novell works with its hardware manufacturing partners to ensure
that their systems installed with SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop can earn
the ENERGY STAR qualification.</para>

<para>By seamlessly providing remote desktop access, Novell aims to
promote more electronic collaboration and even reduce your need for
travel.</para>

</section>
<section label="08_security">
  <title>Keep Your System Secure and Up to Date</title>

  <para>When your system is connected to the Internet, you'll be happy
  to know that we enabled the SUSE Linux Firewall to help secure
  your system and data from intruders. We also include AppArmor,
  the most effective and easy-to-use Linux application security system
  available. It proactively protects the operating system and applications
  from external or internal threats.</para>


<para>In SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop 11, we have introduced a new
granular privilege system PolicyKit that greatly improves the ability
for users and applications to be granted access to privileged operations
when needed. Also in this release, we have improved wireless and wired
network security connectivity and data encryption capabilities.</para>

<para>Novell is dedicated to promptly providing its users with the latest
security updates. To ensure that the latest security patches are installed
on your system, Novell provides a comprehensive resource management
solution that allows you to stay current with all security updates.</para>

</section>
<section label="09_openSUSE">
  <title>openSUSE.org</title> <para>The openSUSE project is a worldwide
  community program sponsored by Novell that promotes the use of
  Linux everywhere.  Please visit opensuse.org where you can find
  and join a community of users and developers, who all have the same
  goal in mind - to create and distribute the world's most usable Linux
  distribution. openSUSE provides the base our award-winning SUSE Linux
  Enterprise products.</para>

<para>The openSUSE Build Service is an open and complete distribution
development platform that provides a transparent infrastructure for
development of the openSUSE distribution. With the openSUSE Build Service,
you can easily find the latest open source packages you are looking
for. It provides a bridge between developers and users with feedback and
rating functionality. For developers it is an efficient place to build
up groups and work together through its project model.</para>

<para>ZYpp is our software management engine and open source project
that powers products like YaST, ZYpper and ZENworks with a powerful
dependency resolver and a convenient package management API.</para>


</section>
<section label="10_easy-management">
  <title>Easy to deploy and manage</title>

<para>SUSE Linux Enterprise supports many deployment strategies
providing system administrators flexible ways to customize and tailor
the distribution to their needs.</para>

<para>AutoYaST is a integrated solution for installing one or more systems
automatically without user intervention. Installations are performed
using a control file with installation and configuration data.</para>

<para>The openSUSE KIWI imaging system provides a complete operating
system image solution for supported hardware platforms as well as
virtualization systems.</para>

<para>With these solutions combined with several key open source projects
such as GConf, PolicyKit and Firstboot, SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop
is the easiest Linux desktop to deploy and manage.</para>

</section>
<section label="11_hardware">
  <title>Certified for SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop</title>

<para>By successfully completing stringent compatibility testing
requirements, Novell's partners qualify their systems for SUSE Linux
Enterprise Desktop certification.</para>

<para>With a system certified for SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop you can
in confidence use our software to manage your media library, collaborate
on projects and stay connected with your friends.</para>

<para>You can find all of the systems that have passed logo certification
by visiting novell.com/desktop. Systems with certification fully take
advantage of SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop to deliver rich Internet
experience, ease of use, and excellent performance.</para>

<para>Novell is pleased to also be part of the Linux Driver Project
focused on working with manufacturers to create and maintain open source
Linux kernel drivers for all types of devices. Timely hardware enablement
for desktop components is achieved by porting drivers to the Linux kernel
that powers SUSE Linux Enterprise.</para>

</section>
<section label="12_interoperability">
  <title>Interoperability: Work with Everyone</title>

<para>SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop is designed with today's heterogeneous
world in mind. It is fully capable to seamlessly integrate into existing
Windows file and print environments. In addition, it plugs into existing
Microsoft Active Directory and Novell eDirectory environments. With
its broad use of open standards, SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop enables
you to share information across any IT system so that you can easily
communicate with all users around you.</para>

<para>OpenOffice.org Novell Edition works with the widest range of
document formats including Open Document Format, Microsoft Office formats
(including OO XML),Works, WordPerfect and others.</para>

<para>Novell is a leader in the Mono project an open source version
of the Microsoft .NET development platform. Its objective is to enable
developers to build and deploy cross-platform .NET Applications. Mono is
the foundation for Moonlight enabling you to enjoy Microsoft Silverlight
content on your Linux desktop.</para>

<para>And, SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop provides accessibility features
so that anyone can take advantage of the improved productivity and lower
cost that a Linux desktop provides.</para>

 </section>
</section>
