<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE section PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY yast "YaST">
<!ENTITY suse "SUSE">
<!ENTITY suselinux "&suse; Linux">
<!ENTITY opensuse "openSUSE">
<!ENTITY suse-version "Leap 42.1">
]>
<!-- <table cellspacing="10" cellpadding="5"> -->
<!--   <tr> -->
<!--     <td valign="top"><img src="&imagedir;/01_welcome.png" width="150" valign="top"></td> -->
<!--     <td> -->
<section>
 <title>Slide Show</title>

 <section label="01_welcome">
  <title>Welcome to openSUSE™!</title>

    <para>
There is a reason why openSUSE is "the makers' choice for sysadmins, developers and desktop users;" openSUSE gives you choice and provides a user-friendly desktop, and feature-rich server environment. People torn between newer software and a long-term, highly stable Linux system turn to openSUSE. &suse-version; provides "The Best of Two Worlds" - reliability and contemporary software. Based on the core of SUSE Linux Enterprise, &suse-version; combines the proven SUSE core with the innovative spirit of open-source communities. That combinations gives makers choices and &suse-version; complements openSUSE's other release Tumbleweed, which caters to those who want continuously updated, tested and new stable packages.
</para>
 </section>

 <section label="02_opensuse">
  <title>openSUSE.org</title>

  <para>
openSUSE is a community project created and sponsored by SUSE to 
deliver the world's most user-friendly computing platform. Many people
from around the world contribute to the openSUSE Project by packaging
software, testing programs, writing documentation, and translating
components into dozens of languages. All of that work is available 
for free in the openSUSE Linux distribution available at www.opensuse.org.
</para>
<para>Visit www.opensuse.org/How_to_Participate to learn how you can join 
the openSUSE community.</para>
 </section>

 <section label="02_z_opensuse">
  <title>openSUSE in Many Languages</title>

  <para>
The openSUSE distribution is available in many languages. Localization
for openSUSE software occurs through the efforts of our hard-working,
community-driven language teams. Thank you to all of our contributors.
Find the localization portal at: http://i18n.opensuse.org/</para>
  
 </section>

 <section label="03_connect">
  <title>Connect and Communicate</title>

<para>
You can communicate more effectively with openSUSE &suse-version; because it
provides a complete set of tools for Web browsing and e-mail
management — it even includes the newest Voice over IP technology.
</para>

<para>openSUSE &suse-version; includes Mozilla Firefox, one of the best Web 
browsers in the world. Firefox includes all the features you need to enjoy
the Web, including the newest HTML5 technologies. Firefox also boasts
lightning-fast performance, and a number of improvements designed to
protect your privacy and prevent phishing attacks.</para>

<para>Also included with openSUSE &suse-version; are Evolution and Kontact, 
complete e-mail and contact management applications. For instant 
messaging, openSUSE features easy to use IM clients that support all 
of the popular protocols: AIM, Facebook, Google Talk, Jabber, MSN,
Yahoo!, Groupwise, and many others.</para> 

 </section>

 <section label="04_create">
  <title>Create, View and Listen</title>
  <para>
Download tunes from the Internet. Rip CDs to create your own customized
music library. Listen to your playlist online. Burn CDs or DVDs. Copy
your files to an iPod or media player and take your music anywhere. Manage
and edit digital pictures with powerful graphics editors. It's all easy
with openSUSE &suse-version;.</para>

 </section>

 <section label="05_office">
  <title>Documents, Spreadsheets and More</title>

  <para>
The openSUSE &suse-version; distribution comes complete with the latest version
of the leading Linux productivity suite, LibreOffice. It features a word
processor, spreadsheet application, HTML editor, presentation designer, and
database manager. It reads and writes multiple formats—including Microsoft
Office formats—so you can move back and forth easily between openSUSE 
and popular non-Linux productivity software. LibreOffice is the perfect 
choice for reports, papers, home budgets, simple graphics and more.</para>
 </section>

<section label="06_graphics">
  <title>Graphics, Graphics, Graphics</title>

  <para>
Using the tools in openSUSE &suse-version;, you can create or edit almost any 
type of graphic. For advanced image manipulation and graphics creation, use The
GIMP a powerful tool for image retouching, composition, and authoring.</para>
 
<para>For vector graphics, openSUSE &suse-version; includes Inkscape — a versatile 
graphics solution delivers support for transparent layers, bitmap tracing, 
text paths and much more.
</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="08_mobility">
  <title>Computing On-the-Go</title>

  <para>openSUSE &suse-version; includes the most advanced mobility features. You
can switch effortlessly between wireless and wired networks using NetworkManager. 
Connect with mobile devices like mobile phones, tablets and PDAs via Bluetooth.</para> 

<para>The newest innovations in power management from openSUSE increase
your mobility and give you the freedom to take your work wherever you
go.
</para>

 </section>

<section label="09_security">
 <title>Your operating system - respecting privacy - providing security</title>

  <para>openSUSE builds something that puts you in control. Rolling or Stable, you decide. Unlike windows, you decide which updates get applied when. Unlike most distros, you decide which desktop you want (or none at all), you have tools like YaST to help you configure your machine and control your security and privacy. Secure your system and data from Internet intruders with SUSE Firewall. This security device is activated by default and easy to configure. But you can do even more to protect your system with openSUSE &suse-version; because it also includes AppArmor, the most effective and
easy-to-use Linux application security system available today. AppArmor proactively protects your operating system and applications from internal or external threats.</para>

<!-- for the online update feature, see bnc#793710 -->
<para>In addition to SUSE Firewall and AppArmor, openSUSE &suse-version; also 
includes a special security patch update system. To ensure that the latest security
patches are installed on your system, you can choose to perform an
online update at the end of this installation procedure (if you did not
choose the automatic installation modus at the beginning). And in the
future, you will be automatically informed of the availability of
important security updates, so you can install them at your convenience.
</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="10_devel">
  <title>Virtualization Technology and Application Development Tools</title>

  <para>Both Xen and KVM hypervisors are included with openSUSE &suse-version;. 
Xen is one of the most robust solutions for virtualization available. In addition, 
openSUSE provides tools for network file sharing (Samba, NFS, etc.), printing (CUPS) 
and Web hosting (Apache). For application development, openSUSE comes with a complete
set of runtime environments plus extensive application development tools.
</para>

 </section>

  <section label="11_docs">
    <title>Learn More</title>
    <para>
openSUSE &suse-version; provides extensive documentation for specific
openSUSE questions as well as general Linux-related questions. The Help
Center is accessible via the main menu. Manuals are also available in
PDF and can be downloaded and printed <!-- translator: check whether a
dedicated page exists for your language and use it instead of "en" -->
(http://en.opensuse.org/Portal:Documentation).

    </para>

    <para>
Even more information is available in the openSUSE wiki at <!--
translator: check whether a dedicated page exists for your language and
use it instead of "en" -->  http://en.opensuse.org/. Under
"Documentation," you'll discover links to useful information created and
maintained by other openSUSE users. You can also find links to the
documentation available on the official SUSE Web site. For help with
specific openSUSE problems, check out the Support Database at
www.opensuse.org
    </para>

<para><!-- translator: adjust the snippet about forums according to your
language; see https://bugzilla.novell.com/show_bug.cgi?id=439101 -->
For support from other openSUSE users, visit the official openSUSE
forums at http://forums.opensuse.org/. Here you'll find thousands of other
openSUSE users, eager to help you get everything you can out of Linux. If 
you're an experienced openSUSE user, the forums are a great place to meet 
other users, and help out other Linux users.
</para>

<para>Want to make openSUSE even better? You can build almost anything 
with openSUSE. It's easy to create and share new packages for multiple 
Linux distributions using the unique and powerful openSUSE Build Service. 
Join openSUSE.org to collaborate.
</para>

  </section>

 <section label="12_suse">
  <title>SUSE and Linux</title>
  <para>
SUSE is committed to your success with Linux. In addition to openSUSE,
SUSE also delivers an exciting suite of products designed to meet the
needs of businesses large and small.</para>

  <para>
The enterprise Linux products from SUSE include SUSE Linux Enterprise Server and
SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop. Our enterprise products are delivered with a 
10 year maintenance guarantee out of the box with the possibility of extending 
it to 13 years as well as other optional support programs. 
For more information on enterprise Linux from SUSE, visit http://www.suse.com
</para>

 </section>

</section>
