<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE section PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY yast "YaST">
<!ENTITY suse "SUSE">
<!ENTITY suselinux "&suse; Linux">
<!ENTITY opensuse "openSUSE">
<!ENTITY suse-version "10.3">
]>
<!-- <table cellspacing="10" cellpadding="5"> -->
<!--   <tr> -->
<!--     <td valign="top"><img src="&imagedir;/01_welcome.png" width="150" valign="top"></td> -->
<!--     <td> -->

<section>
 <title>Slide Show</title>

 <section label="01_welcome">
  <title>Welcome to openSUSE</title>

    <para>
Whether you use your computer to communicate with friends, relatives, or
colleagues, manage and enjoy your pictures and music, browse the Internet for
the latest news or information, write a report or budget, or host a personal
Web site or home network, you will find everything you need in openSUSE
&suse-version;
</para>
 </section>

 <section label="02_opensuse">
  <title>openSUSE.org</title>

  <para>This distribution is created by the openSUSE.org project. The
  openSUSE project, sponsored by Novell, is a collaborative community
  effort to deliver the world's most usable open source computing
  platform, the openSUSE distribution. Hosted at opensuse.org, many individuals
  are involved in packaging software, testing programs, writing documentation,
  and also localizing components.</para>
  
  <para>openSUSE is available in many languages. Localization for openSUSE
  specific software is done by community-driven language teams. Find the
  localization portal at http://i18n.opensuse.org/ .</para>
  
  <para>Visit www.opensuse.org to learn how you can join the openSUSE
  community.</para>
  
  

 </section>

 <section label="03_connect">
  <title>Connect and Communicate</title>

  <para>openSUSE &suse-version; provides a complete set of tools for Web
  browsing and e-mail management and even includes the newest Internet-based
  phone technology.</para>
 
  <para>The Firefox Web browser is one of the best Web browser in the market. It
  boasts a complete set of browser features, including Java, Adobe Reader,
  RealPlayer, and Macromedia Flash plug-ins, plus lightning-fast
  performance.</para>
 
  <para>Novell Evolution and Kontact are complete e-mail and contact managers
  that you can use to manage all your mail accounts. openSUSE also includes
  state-of-the-art Internet-based (VoIP) solutions that let you call
  people connected to the Internet all over the world.</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="04_create">
  <title>Create, View, and Listen</title>
  <para>Download tunes from the Internet. Rip CDs to create your own customized
  music library. Listen to your playlist online. Burn a CD or DVD. Even copy
  your files to an iPod or similar device to take your music anywhere. Manage
  and edit digital pictures with powerful graphics editors. It is easy with
  openSUSE.</para>

 </section>

 <section label="05_office">
  <title>Documents, Spreadsheets, and More</title>

  <para>openSUSE &suse-version; comes complete with the latest version of the
  leading Linux productivity suite, OpenOffice.org. Openoffice.org includes
  a word processor, spreadsheet application, HTML editor, presentation
  designer, and database.  It also reads and writes files you can use with
  popular non-Linux productivity software. It is the perfect choice for
  reports, papers, home budgets, and simple graphics.</para>
 </section>

<section label="06_graphics">
  <title>Graphics, Graphics, Graphics</title>

  <para>With the tools in openSUSE, you can create or edit practically any kind
  of graphics. For advanced image manipulation and graphics creation, use
  powerful tools like the GIMP, a complete image retouching, composition, and
  authoring tool. </para>
 
  <para>For vector graphics, try Inkscape, a versatile graphics solution
  complete with support for transparent layers, bitmap tracing, text paths, and
  much more.</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="08_mobility">
  <title>Computing On-the-Go</title>

  <para> openSUSE includes the most advanced mobility features. Switch between
  wireless and wired networks using NetworkManager. Connect with mobile devices
  like mobile phones and PDAs via Bluetooth. Use infrared ports to synchronize
  your data. Newest innovations in power management increase your
  mobility.</para>

 </section>

<section label="09_security">
 <title>Keep Your System Secure and Up-to-Date</title>

  <para>SUSE Firewall helps secure your system and data from Internet
  intruders. It is activated by default and easy to configure. openSUSE also
  includes AppArmor, the most effective and easy-to-use Linux application
  security system available today.  It proactively protects the operating
  system and applications from external or internal threats.</para>

  <para>openSUSE also includes a special security patch update system. To
    ensure that the latest security patches are installed on your system,
    choose to perform an online update at the end of this installation
    procedure. In the future, you will be informed of the availability of
    important security updates, so you can install them at your convenience.
</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="10_devel">
  <title>Virtualization Technology and Application Development Tools</title>

  <para>openSUSE includes the highest performing virtualization software, the
  XEN hypervisor. In addition, openSUSE provides tools for network file
  sharing, printing (Samba) and Web hosting (Apache). For application development,
  openSUSE comes with a complete set of runtime environments plus extensive
  application development tools, including KDevelop, Eclipse, and Mono. Almost
  everything can be build with openSUSE.</para>

  <para>Join openSUSE.org to collaborate. Create and share new packages for
  multiple Linux distribution using the unique and powerful openSUSE Build
  Service.</para>
 
 </section>

  <section label="11_docs">
    <title>Learn More</title>
    <para>openSUSE provides extensive documentation for SUSE-specific as well
    as  general Linux-related questions. The SUSE Help Center is accessible via
    the main menu. Manuals are also available in PDF-format and can be
    downloaded and printed
<!-- translator: check whether a dedicated page exists for your language
           and use it instead of "en" -->
(http://en.opensuse.org/Documentation).
    </para>

    <para>
      Even more information is available in the openSUSE wiki at
      <!-- translator: check whether a dedicated page exists for your language
           and use it instead of "en" -->
      http://en.opensuse.org/.  In Documentation, find links to all sorts of
      useful information created and maintained by other openSUSE users. Also
      find links to the documentation available on the Novell Web site.  For
      help with specific problems with openSUSE, check out the Support
      Database.
    </para>
  </section>

 <section label="12_novell">
  <title>Novell and Linux</title>
  <para>
Novell is committed to your success with Linux.  Besides openSUSE, Novell
delivers an exciting suite of products designed to meet the needs of businesses
large and small.</para>

  <para>
The enterprise Linux products from Novell include SUSE Linux Enterprise Server,
SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop, and Novell Open Enterprise Server. Our
enterprise products are delivered with a seven year maintenance guarantee,
optional support programs, and a unique Linux indemnification program.
</para>

 </section>

</section>
