<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE section PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.2//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.2/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY yast "YaST">
<!ENTITY suse "SUSE">
<!ENTITY suselinux "&suse; Linux">
<!ENTITY opensuse "openSUSE">
<!ENTITY suse-version "10.3">
]>
<!-- <table cellspacing="10" cellpadding="5"> -->
<!--   <tr> -->
<!--     <td valign="top"><img src="&imagedir;/01_welcome.png" width="150" valign="top"></td> -->
<!--     <td> -->

<section>
 <title>Slide Show</title>

 <section label="01_welcome">
  <title>Welcome to openSUSE</title>

    <para>
Whether you use your computer to communicate with friends, relatives, or
colleagues, manage and enjoy your pictures and music, browse the Internet for
the latest news or information, write a report or budget, or host a personal
Web site or home network, you will find everything you need in openSUSE
&suse-version;
</para>
 </section>

 <section label="02_opensuse">
  <title>openSUSE.org</title>

  <para>This distribution is created by the openSUSE.org project. The
  openSUSE project, sponsored by Novell, is a collaborative community
  effort to deliver the world's most usable open source computing
  platform, the openSUSE distribution. Hosted at opensuse.org, the
  project features a transparent development process, simple
  participation models, extensive development tools, and easy access
  to builds and releases for everyone.  Visit www.opensuse.org to learn
  how you can join the openSUSE community.</para>
 </section>

 <section label="02_05_localization">
  <title>openSUSE Localization</title>

  <para>The openSUSE project is a community project and many individuals are
  involved in packaging software, testing programs, writing documentation, and
  also localizing components.  Localization for openSUSE specific software is
  done by language teams.  Find the localization portal at
  http://i18n.opensuse.org/ .</para>
 </section>

 <section label="03_connect">
  <title>Connect and Communicate</title>

  <para>openSUSE &suse-version; provides a complete set of tools for Web
  browsing and e-mail management and even includes the newest Internet-based
  phone technology.</para>
 
  <para>The Firefox Web browser is the best Web browser in the market. It
  boasts a complete set of browser features, including Java, Adobe Reader,
  RealPlayer, and Macromedia Flash plug-ins, plus lightning-fast
  performance.</para>
 
  <para>Novell Evolution and Kontact are complete e-mail and contact managers
  that you can use to manage all your mail accounts. openSUSE also includes
  Linphone and Twinkle, Internet-based (VoIP) solutions that let you call
  people connected to the Internet all over the world.</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="04_create">
  <title>Create, View, and Listen</title>
  <para>Download tunes from the Internet. Rip CDs to create your own customized
  music library. Listen to your playlist online. Burn a CD or DVD. Even copy
  your files to an iPod or similar device to take your music anywhere. Manage
  and edit digital pictures with powerful graphics editors. It is easy with
  openSUSE.</para>

 </section>

 <section label="05_office">
  <title>Documents, Spreadsheets, and More</title>

  <para>openSUSE &suse-version; comes complete with the latest version of the
  leading Linux productivity suite, OpenOffice.org 2.0. Openoffice.org includes
  a word processor, spreadsheet application, HTML editor, presentation
  designer, and database.  It also reads and writes files you can use with
  popular non-Linux productivity software. It is the perfect choice for
  reports, papers, home budgets, and simple graphics.</para>
 
 </section>

<section label="06_graphics">
  <title>Graphics, Graphics, Graphics</title>
  <para>With the tools in openSUSE, you can create or edit practically any
  kind of graphics. For advanced image manipulation and graphics creation, use
  the GIMP, a complete image retouching, composition, and
  authoring tool. GIMP has enough features to satisfy the most exacting
  artist.</para>
 
  <para>For vector graphics, try Inkscape, a versatile graphics solution
  complete with support for transparent layers, bitmap tracing, text paths, and
  much more.</para>
 
 </section>

<section label="07_kde">
  <title>The Latest Desktop Innovations</title>
  <para>openSUSE provides you with a choice of the most usable graphical
  desktop environments. Choose from the most up-to-date Linux graphical
  environments--GNOME and KDE--each combining ease of use,
  contemporary functionality, and outstanding graphical design with the
  technological superiority of the Linux operating system.</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="08_mobility">
  <title>Computing On-the-Go</title>

  <para>If you run Linux on a laptop, you will be glad you chose openSUSE. It
  includes the most advanced mobility features. Switch between wireless and
  wired networks with our NetworkManager, connect with mobile phones and PDAs
  that support Bluetooth, and even use infrared ports to synchronize with cell
  phones or PalmOS devices. Of course, USB memory sticks are no
  problem. Finally, new power management features give you the option to
  "suspend" your session, saving it to disk or RAM. Not only does suspend allow
  you to turn off and restart the system faster, but when you do restart,
  you are exactly where you were when you stopped.</para>

 </section>

<section label="09_security">
 <title>Keep Your System Secure and Up-to-Date</title>
  <para>If your system is connected to the Internet, SUSE Firewall helps secure
   your system and data from Internet 
   intruders. Leaving it activated gives you enormous protection and configuring
  it to your needs takes only a moment.  openSUSE also includes AppArmor,
  the most effective and easy-to-use Linux application
  security system available today.  It proactively protects the operating
  system and applications from external or internal threats.</para>

  <para>openSUSE also includes a special security patch update system. As
    security patches are created for the Linux kernel and packages included in
    openSUSE, we make those available to you on a special update server. To
    ensure that the latest security patches are installed on your system,
    choose to perform an online update at the end of this installation
    procedure. In the future, the update system keeps you informed of the
    availability of important security updates, so you can install them at your
    convenience.
</para>
 
 </section>

 <section label="10_devel">
  <title>Powerful Home Networking and Application Development Tools</title>

  <para>openSUSE includes tools for network file sharing and printing (Samba),
  Web hosting (Apache), and virtualization (Xen). For application development,
  openSUSE comes with a complete set of runtime environments plus extensive
  application development tools, including KDevelop, Eclipse, and Mono. That
  means that if you can imagine it, you can probably build it with openSUSE.
  At openSUSE.org, you can join with thousands of other openSUSE
  users to collaborate and create powerful new packages that you can
  use.</para>
 
 </section>

  <section label="11_docs">
    <title>Learn More with Documentation</title>
    <para>openSUSE includes both SUSE-specific and general Linux
      documentation.  The SUSE Help Center, available from the main menu or
      with the susehelp command, provides one-stop access to all the help
      included with your system.  For example, use it to read the SUSE manuals,
      man pages, and info pages.  If you want to print your own copy of the
      manuals, you can download a PDF version.  Find the URL for the PDFs at
      <!-- translator: check whether a dedicated page exists for your language
           and use it instead of "en" -->
      http://en.opensuse.org/Documentation.
    </para>

    <para>
      Even more documentation is available in the openSUSE wiki at
      <!-- translator: check whether a dedicated page exists for your language
           and use it instead of "en" -->
      http://en.opensuse.org/.  In Documentation, find links to all sorts of
      useful information created and maintained by other openSUSE users. Also
      find links to the documentation available on the Novell Web site.  For
      help with specific problems with openSUSE, check out the Support
      Database.
    </para>
  </section>

 <section label="12_novell">
  <title>Novell and Linux</title>
  <para>
Novell is committed to your success with Linux.
Besides openSUSE, Novell delivers an exciting suite of products designed
 to meet the needs of businesses large and small.</para>

  <para>
The enterprise Linux products from Novell include SUSE Linux Enterprise Server,
SUSE Linux Enterprise Desktop, and Novell Open Enterprise Server. Our
enterprise products are delivered with a seven year maintenance guarantee,
optional support programs, and a unique Linux indemnification program.
</para>

 </section>

</section>
